# Ahmed Mohamed

# Front-end developer

Address Cairo, Egypt

Phone 01124269532

Date of birth 1993-08-01

E-mail ahmed.m.moneem@gmail.com

GitHub https://ahmedmohamed26.github.io/

#### LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/iahmedmohame

#### **Facebook**

https://web.facebook.com/iAhmmedMohame

d



Hi, i'am Ahmed Mohamed an energetic and enthusiastic frontend web developer eager to learn new technologies and build amazing stuff.I'm 25 years old ,up I am enjoying building elegant and professional web pages in a modern way. I have developed my skills in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Angular and other skills to help me fulfill high qualifications.

## **Experience**

### 2019-05 - present Front-end developer

proemcs

#### Responsibilities:

- · Responsibility For Restful APIs
- Convert PSD || ProtoType To PugJS & SCSS
- · Minify & Compressing
- · Performance And Usability Testing

#### 2018-01 - 2019-04

#### Front-end developer

Valux apps

### Responsibilities:

- · Responsibility For Restful APIs
- Convert PSD | | ProtoType To PugJS & SCSS
- · Minify & Compressing
- Performance And Usability Testing

### **Education**

#### 2011-09 - 2015-07

# **Cairo Higher institutes**

I am a graduate of systems and informations Bachelor degree ,Cairo Higher institutes in Mokattam (2015)

### Skills

Angular 7

ionic 4

React js

Typescript

Es6

Javascript

SCSS

Pug js

Gulp js

Bootstrap 4

jquery

Git

HTML5

CSS3

XD